<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-09-19T16:32:58+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Ladno Developer Portfolio</title><subtitle>Software and Games</subtitle><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><entry><title type="html">Dungeon Forge</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/software/2024/03/26/dungeon-forge.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dungeon Forge" /><published>2024-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/software/2024/03/26/dungeon-forge</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/software/2024/03/26/dungeon-forge.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="overview">Overview</h1>
<p>Dungeon Forge is a Godot 4 extension plugin that allows users to generate dungeon-like layouts in their scenes with a click of a button. This plugin opens a new window in the Godot 4 editor in the bottom right corner where users can select from three different biomes: dungeons, wooden cabins, and frozen caves. Upon selecting the gridmap generator in the menu, a new pop-up menu on the right allows users to set parameters for the dungeon layouts and then generate the layouts and meshes. Additional features include a first-person controller that allows users to explore generated dungeons, saving generated layouts, and reusing dungeons.</p>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: center; align-items: center; margin: 20px 0;">
    <iframe width="660" height="415" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dw3r8JJGyQ4?si=kLD1VK-v1A9r4Cv3" title="Dungeon Forge Demo" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">
    </iframe>
</div>

<h1 id="features">Features</h1>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Biome Selection</strong>: Choose from three biomes: dungeons, wooden cabins, and frozen caves.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Gridmap Generator</strong>: Customize parameters and generate dungeon layouts and meshes.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>First Person Controller</strong>: Explore the generated dungeons in first-person view.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Save and Reuse</strong>: Save generated layouts and reuse them in your scenes.<br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="in-future-development">In Future Development</h1>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Multiple Floor Layouts</strong>: Create multiple floors connected by ladders or stairs.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Upload Your Mesh</strong>: Allow users to drag and drop their mesh to become the new theme they would use.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Fix Bugs</strong>: Fix bugs. One big one currently is save disappearing on client restart. <br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="installation">Installation</h1>
<ol>
  <li>Clone https://github.com/Ladnopoka/Godot-room-generator-plugin.git</li>
  <li>Add the “addons/room-generator” folder to the “addons” folder in your Godot project</li>
  <li>In Godot editor, select “Project” in the top left corner</li>
  <li>Go to “Project Settings…”</li>
  <li>Go to “Plugins” tab</li>
  <li>Click “Enable” tick box for the “Dungeon Forge” plugin</li>
  <li>You should now see a new UI window appearing in bottom right corner of the editor</li>
  <li>To spawn a dungeon generator, select “Gridmap Generator” in either of the themes</li>
</ol>

<h1 id="contact">Contact</h1>
<h5 id="for-any-inquiries-or-feedback-feel-free-to-reach-out-to">For any inquiries or feedback, feel free to reach out to:</h5>

<p><strong>Jevgenij Ivanov</strong> <br />
<strong>Email</strong>: ladnopokaa@gmail.com <br /><br />
<strong>GitHub</strong>: https://github.com/Ladnopoka <br />
<strong>itch.io</strong>: https://ladnogames.itch.io/ <br />
<strong>YouTube</strong>: https://www.youtube.com/@LadnoDev <br />
<strong>X</strong>: https://x.com/Ladnopokaa <br />
<strong>Discord</strong>: Ladno#3352</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="software" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Dungeon Forge is a Godot 4 extension plugin that allows users to generate dungeon-like layouts in their scenes with a click of a button. This plugin opens a new window in the Godot 4 editor in the bottom right corner where users can select from three different biomes: dungeons, wooden cabins, and frozen caves. Upon selecting the gridmap generator in the menu, a new pop-up menu on the right allows users to set parameters for the dungeon layouts and then generate the layouts and meshes. Additional features include a first-person controller that allows users to explore generated dungeons, saving generated layouts, and reusing dungeons.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Spotify Playlist Enhancer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/software/2024/01/12/spotify-playlist-enhancer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spotify Playlist Enhancer" /><published>2024-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/software/2024/01/12/spotify-playlist-enhancer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/software/2024/01/12/spotify-playlist-enhancer.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="overview">Overview</h1>
<p>Google Chrome extension which allows you to connect to Spotify API fetch songs and playlist from your Spotify account.
This extension also allows you to retrieve your top 5 played tracks, and give you 5 recommendations based on these tracks, all with a couple of clicks through the extension UI.
Finally, you can generate a Spotify playlist with the songs that were recommended to you, and play these songs inside the extension right there and now.
When the playlists are generated, they are added to your Spotify account, however, in the extension UI, you can select to not keep the playlist if you don’t like it after listening to the recommended songs.<br /><br /></p>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: center; align-items: center; margin: 20px 0;">
    <iframe width="660" height="415" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NTn2MuQhe8Q?si=fydHOFu14HMk2qo1" title="Spotify Playlist Enhancer Demo" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">
    </iframe>
</div>

<h1 id="features">Features</h1>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Authenticate Spotify Account</strong>: Securely connect your Spotify account to the extension.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Top 5 Played Tracks</strong>: View your top 5 most played tracks on Spotify.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Top 5 Recommended Tracks</strong>: Get recommendations from Spotify based on your top played tracks.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Generate New Playlists</strong>: Create new playlists with new songs based on your top tracks and recommendations.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Play Songs in Browser</strong>: Listen to your playlists directly within Google Chrome.<br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="in-development">In Development</h1>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Dynamic Playlist Manager</strong>: Drag and drop songs to create the perfect playlist.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Customized Profile</strong>: Personalize your extension profile.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Friend System</strong>: Connect with friends and share your music preferences.<br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="installation">Installation</h1>
<ol>
  <li>Clone https://github.com/Ladnopoka/Spotify-Playlist-Enhancer.git</li>
  <li>Go to ./spotify-playlist-enhancer directory</li>
  <li>Run command “npm install react-scripts”</li>
  <li>Run command “npm install fireabase”</li>
  <li>Run command “npm run build” in your terminal/console from spotify-playlist-enhancer directory</li>
  <li>The spotify-playlist-enhancer directory now has a new folder “build”</li>
  <li>Open your Google Chrome browser and go to your extensions</li>
  <li>In the top right corner of the extensions page, toggle developer mode</li>
  <li>A couple of new buttons appear, select “Load unpacked”</li>
  <li>Select the build folder that you created in step 2</li>
  <li>The extension now appears in your extensions, enable it and you will have the icon in extensions (top left corner)</li>
</ol>

<h1 id="contact">Contact</h1>
<h5 id="for-any-inquiries-or-feedback-feel-free-to-reach-out-to">For any inquiries or feedback, feel free to reach out to:</h5>

<p><strong>Jevgenij Ivanov</strong> <br />
<strong>Email</strong>: ladnopokaa@gmail.com <br /><br />
<strong>GitHub</strong>: https://github.com/Ladnopoka <br />
<strong>itch.io</strong>: https://ladnogames.itch.io/ <br />
<strong>YouTube</strong>: https://www.youtube.com/@LadnoDev <br />
<strong>X</strong>: https://x.com/Ladnopokaa <br />
<strong>Discord</strong>: Ladno#3352</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="software" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Google Chrome extension which allows you to connect to Spotify API fetch songs and playlist from your Spotify account. This extension also allows you to retrieve your top 5 played tracks, and give you 5 recommendations based on these tracks, all with a couple of clicks through the extension UI. Finally, you can generate a Spotify playlist with the songs that were recommended to you, and play these songs inside the extension right there and now. When the playlists are generated, they are added to your Spotify account, however, in the extension UI, you can select to not keep the playlist if you don’t like it after listening to the recommended songs.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Slayer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2023/10/02/slayer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Slayer" /><published>2023-10-02T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-10-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2023/10/02/slayer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2023/10/02/slayer.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="overview">Overview</h1>
<p>Slayer is an exciting top-down isometric roguelike game that immerses players in a world of strategic combat and character progression. Choose from three distinct classes—Mage, Barbarian, and Rogue—and embark on thrilling adventures, battling fierce enemies and mastering powerful abilities.</p>

<h1 id="features">Features</h1>
<h4 id="three-playable-classes">Three Playable Classes:</h4>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Mage</strong>: Harness the power of magic to unleash devastating spells like the Lightning Storm.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Barbarian</strong>: Engage in brutal melee combat with unmatched strength.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Rogue</strong>: Utilize agility and stealth to outmaneuver enemies and strike with precision.<br /></li>
</ul>

<h4 id="other-features">Other Features:</h4>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Interactive Hideout</strong>: Start your journey in the Hideout, where all three characters await. Click on any character to control and test their abilities before heading into battle.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Dynamic Battlegrounds</strong>: Teleport from the Hideout to various battlegrounds where enemies challenge your skills. Use WASD for movement and mouse clicks to attack.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Experience and Progression</strong>: Gain experience with each enemy defeated, leveling up your character and enhancing their abilities.<br /></li>
  <li><strong>Spells and Abilities</strong>: Each character class has unique spells and abilities. For example, the Mage can cast a powerful Lightning Storm using the Q key.<br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="in-development">In Development</h1>
<ul>
  <li>Adding more skills and ways to kill enemies</li>
  <li>Developing better progression system with experience</li>
  <li>Inventory System: Manage your items and equipment to enhance your character’s capabilities.</li>
  <li>Online Global Leaderboard: Compete with players worldwide to see who has the highest character level, most kills, and the best class performance.<br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="controls">Controls</h1>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Movement</strong>: WASD keys <br /></li>
  <li><strong>Attack</strong>: Mouse click <br /></li>
  <li><strong>Special Ability (Mage)</strong>: Q key <br /></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="installation">Installation</h1>
<ol>
  <li>Download the game from Slayer on itch.io.</li>
  <li>Extract the downloaded files.</li>
  <li>Run the executable file to start playing. <br /></li>
</ol>

<h1 id="contact">Contact</h1>
<h5 id="for-any-inquiries-or-feedback-feel-free-to-reach-out-to">For any inquiries or feedback, feel free to reach out to:</h5>

<p><strong>Jevgenij Ivanov</strong> <br />
<strong>Email</strong>: ladnopokaa@gmail.com <br /><br />
<strong>GitHub</strong>: https://github.com/Ladnopoka <br />
<strong>itch.io</strong>: https://ladnogames.itch.io/ <br />
<strong>YouTube</strong>: https://www.youtube.com/@LadnoDev <br />
<strong>X</strong>: https://x.com/Ladnopokaa <br />
<strong>Discord</strong>: Ladno#3352</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="games" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Slayer is an exciting top-down isometric roguelike game that immerses players in a world of strategic combat and character progression. Choose from three distinct classes—Mage, Barbarian, and Rogue—and embark on thrilling adventures, battling fierce enemies and mastering powerful abilities.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Combat Clicker</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2022/03/22/combat-clicker.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Combat Clicker" /><published>2022-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2022/03/22/combat-clicker</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2022/03/22/combat-clicker.html"><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center; margin-top: -20px; margin-bottom: 25px; scale: 1.4">
  <a href="/games/combat_clicker/views/index.html" target="_blank" class="btn btn-primary" style="padding: 10px 20px; font-size: 1.2em;">Play CombatClicker.io</a>
</div>

<h1 id="overview">Overview</h1>
<p><strong>Combat Clicker</strong> is a browser-based, turn-based game where you face off against a cunning rat warrior. Your goal is simple: get lucky and guess the right option to defeat the rat! The game features a mix of attack and defense options, requiring players to choose where to strike and where to defend.</p>

<h1 id="game-presentation">Game Presentation</h1>
<p>Project presentation video where I showcase the game and my teammate covers the work on the game menus, click on the image to see:</p>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: center; align-items: center; margin: 20px 0;">
    <iframe width="660" height="415" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Mptg1MEHPik?si=Go7BpwS23VTs78SS" title="Combat Clicker" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">
    </iframe>
</div>

<h1 id="how-to-play">How to Play</h1>
<ol>
  <li>Select the positions where to attack the Rat Warrior.</li>
  <li>Defend two positions from attacks of the Rat Warrior.</li>
  <li>Observe the Combat Log and try to win!</li>
</ol>

<h3 id="choose-your-attack">Choose Your Attack:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Pick <strong>2 out of 5 possible attack positions</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Head</li>
      <li>Body</li>
      <li>Legs</li>
      <li>Arms</li>
      <li>Waist</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<h3 id="defend-against-the-rat-warrior">Defend Against the Rat Warrior:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>The rat will retaliate! You must guess where it will strike and choose <strong>2 out of 5 positions</strong> to defend:
    <ul>
      <li>Head</li>
      <li>Body</li>
      <li>Legs</li>
      <li>Arms</li>
      <li>Waist</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>If you guess correctly, you block the damage; if not, you’ll take a hit.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="combat-log">Combat Log:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>The game features a <strong>combat log</strong> that keeps track of all the damage dealt and received during the fight.</li>
  <li>It’s a great way to see how well you’re doing.</li>
</ul>

<h1 id="contact">Contact</h1>
<h5 id="for-any-inquiries-or-feedback-feel-free-to-reach-out-to">For any inquiries or feedback, feel free to reach out to:</h5>

<p><strong>Jevgenij Ivanov</strong> <br />
<strong>Email</strong>: ladnopokaa@gmail.com <br /><br />
<strong>GitHub</strong>: https://github.com/Ladnopoka <br />
<strong>itch.io</strong>: https://ladnogames.itch.io/ <br />
<strong>YouTube</strong>: https://www.youtube.com/@LadnoDev <br />
<strong>X</strong>: https://x.com/Ladnopokaa <br />
<strong>Discord</strong>: Ladno#3352</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="games" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Play CombatClicker.io]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Enlightenment</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/28/enlightenment.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Enlightenment" /><published>2018-01-28T22:43:01+00:00</published><updated>2018-01-28T22:43:01+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/28/enlightenment</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/28/enlightenment.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="a-bad-start-a-good-start">A bad start, A good start.</h1>
<p>It all started with the American elections of 2016 December. I remember waking up one day, astounded. I had gone to bed the previous night thinking how bonkers it would be if Trump won the elections.
<br />How could this seemingly insane person win the freakin’ elections? This sparked my interest in American politics. Everyone in my circle had been bashing and ridiculing this guy for months.
<br />I started out the traditional way, watching videos of ignorant Trump followers. It was fun while it lasted; witnessing horribly ignorant people making a fool of themselves on the internet. These people lacked common sense, and a general understanding of the world.
<br />The curiosity gradually receded, and I got busy with other things.
<br />Months later, I was back, now binging on liberal-bashing vids, which was a result of watching those SJW bashing vids, which was a result of watching those instant Karma vids, which was a result of watching those public outrage vids (I used to stay up real late at nights, with no purpose those days).
<br />Ah, the liberals were making fools of themselves too! <em>Faith in humanity restored.</em> These sjws were rebels without cause. Aren’t we all? They were fighting against oppression, injustice, bigotry, racism, sexism, chauvinism, and a litany of evils. But so carried away they were, that somewhere, they had lost their point and were sometimes fighting a lost cause, sometimes a non-existent cause. In a bunch of these videos, I saw this one man so effortlessly destroy people in debate. And he did it with charm and disdain. He had something about him. He wore a smile on his face all along, making sly, snarky, witty remarks at the opposition profusely. I also saw another man debating about transgender rights, and if its a valid gender at all, or it should just be considered as gender dysphoria. Just Google ‘Ben Shapiro The Boy scouts vid’. This person maintained a serious and an honest demeanor, but was very trenchant and snarky nonetheless. Both these people belonged to the right. They are Milo Yiannopoulos and Ben Shapiro respectively. Their style of communication and debate excited me, and pulled me to watch more videos of them just crushing their opponents. Also this guy, Steven crowder, is a good debater. Many of these Sjw and feminist bashing vids were very right wing inclined. The truth is, you can find videos of both the sides destroying the other side if you merely provide the search term. Now, this brings really disturbing effects. What happens is this traps us in a bubble of our own political ideologies by reinforcing our views. After all, the whole society is just make-believe. What these people believe is that winning an argument makes us right. <em>REKT. GOT HIM. NOPE.</em> Just for the heck of it, watch a few videos holding the exact opposite ideology of your views. Gain some perspective. It’s an insidious world out there on the internet.
<br />Stay informed.</p>

<h1 id="inspiration-from-an-unexpected-source">Inspiration from an unexpected source</h1>
<p><br />Mags shared a link on Youtube once. It was a couple of <em>Pranic healers</em> on a NEWS channel claiming to cure illnesses through phone. They were speaking all sorts of gibberish and trying to make a living through chicanery. One person showed up 20 minutes into the news interview. His first line was “What is this nonsense?” The news anchor had been meek, but not this guy. This one wanted to prove a point. And he did. He proved LIVE on Television that these people were nothing more than quacks. The look on his face showed his contempt for this absurdity. More noteworthy was his insight into science and history, and his proficiency in English and Telugu as well. <em>This was BBG!</em><br />Babu Gogineni, the cutie pie sent here to exterminate lies and delusions and bring 20-20 vision back in place for the society . I’ve since watched more than a hundred vids of this guy swooshing into news debates, tearing the ignorants apart with science and logic and conscience. His prey were <em>past-life therapists, astro psychologists, numerologists, celebrity astrologers, priests, pseudo scientists</em>, and other proponents of flawed dogma. He one-handedly raised serious questions about the state our state, our country and the rest of the world is in. He was all about Rationalism.
<br />All this binge-watching raised some <em>serious questions</em>.
<br />Is Religion the root of all problems? How deeply rooted was I in religion and blind faith and superstitions? How deeply rooted was my family?<br />I’m an Atheist, but my belief was slowly being supplanted by false beliefs, just because literally everyone around me wasn’t even talking about this, and I was about to cave in to this ideology.<br />I distinctly remember the Teachers’ day gaffe, where I called-up 2 of my close friends at midnight since the moon had a halo around, and my father had told me that it forshadowed humongous disasters. I was really embarrassed when nothing happened the next day.</p>

<h1 id="analogy">Analogy</h1>
<p>See how scary it is in North Korea. Kim Jong Un is THE God. People literally cry when they get to see him. Children are made to pray in his honor in schools everyday, when we know he’s not (I’d recommend that you watch the VICE documentary series on North Korea). It’s a saddening life that they lead, not knowing how the rest of the world is, horribly restricted by the law of the land, most of the country without electricity at night. How absurd it is, right?<br />Wait, there’s already something like it in the rest of the world. It’s religion. And it’s institutionalized too!<br /> Don’t go out during an eclipse. You will have serious health problems this year. But, perform this simple pooja for a nominal amount, and I can make it void!
The problem with religion is, it’s been left unquestioned for far too long that people have taken it to be true.<br />And questioning something that we’ve been brainwashed about all our lives, generation after generation, every single day, will just turn these people against us. The idea has been too deeply planted.<br />We’ve been taught this since we were kids. Kids are stupid. They believe what we tell them. Tell them blue is orange, they will believe blue is orange. Tell them there is a world in outer space, with flying elephants and a world at the earth’s crest with demons with horns, <em>THEY WILL BELIEVE IT</em>. That is the most critical time in a person’s growth, and these people are targeting the impressionable kids. Anyway, that’s a topic for another day.
<br />Talking about Babu again, I like his approach to debate as well-Zero tolerance, zero fucks given to sweet talking.
<br /></p>
<blockquote>
  <p>One final question, Is it enough to win the debate? And does majority mean correctness?</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="other" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bad start, A good start. It all started with the American elections of 2016 December. I remember waking up one day, astounded. I had gone to bed the previous night thinking how bonkers it would be if Trump won the elections. How could this seemingly insane person win the freakin’ elections? This sparked my interest in American politics. Everyone in my circle had been bashing and ridiculing this guy for months. I started out the traditional way, watching videos of ignorant Trump followers. It was fun while it lasted; witnessing horribly ignorant people making a fool of themselves on the internet. These people lacked common sense, and a general understanding of the world. The curiosity gradually receded, and I got busy with other things. Months later, I was back, now binging on liberal-bashing vids, which was a result of watching those SJW bashing vids, which was a result of watching those instant Karma vids, which was a result of watching those public outrage vids (I used to stay up real late at nights, with no purpose those days). Ah, the liberals were making fools of themselves too! Faith in humanity restored. These sjws were rebels without cause. Aren’t we all? They were fighting against oppression, injustice, bigotry, racism, sexism, chauvinism, and a litany of evils. But so carried away they were, that somewhere, they had lost their point and were sometimes fighting a lost cause, sometimes a non-existent cause. In a bunch of these videos, I saw this one man so effortlessly destroy people in debate. And he did it with charm and disdain. He had something about him. He wore a smile on his face all along, making sly, snarky, witty remarks at the opposition profusely. I also saw another man debating about transgender rights, and if its a valid gender at all, or it should just be considered as gender dysphoria. Just Google ‘Ben Shapiro The Boy scouts vid’. This person maintained a serious and an honest demeanor, but was very trenchant and snarky nonetheless. Both these people belonged to the right. They are Milo Yiannopoulos and Ben Shapiro respectively. Their style of communication and debate excited me, and pulled me to watch more videos of them just crushing their opponents. Also this guy, Steven crowder, is a good debater. Many of these Sjw and feminist bashing vids were very right wing inclined. The truth is, you can find videos of both the sides destroying the other side if you merely provide the search term. Now, this brings really disturbing effects. What happens is this traps us in a bubble of our own political ideologies by reinforcing our views. After all, the whole society is just make-believe. What these people believe is that winning an argument makes us right. REKT. GOT HIM. NOPE. Just for the heck of it, watch a few videos holding the exact opposite ideology of your views. Gain some perspective. It’s an insidious world out there on the internet. Stay informed.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Outbreak</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/12/outbreak.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Outbreak" /><published>2018-01-12T15:35:35+00:00</published><updated>2018-01-12T15:35:35+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/12/outbreak</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/12/outbreak.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="what-gets-em-high">What gets ‘em high?</h1>
<p>“We’re trying to shoot them down?” Su asked.
<br />“That does nothing” the General scoffed.
He continued, “We need to blow ‘em up. That’s our only shot.”<br />
“And how do we do that” Su was thinking out loud.
<br />“Bait and switch. We fill up the bunkers with their “fix”.”
<br />“Coke? The F2 variant?” Su knew the plan.
<br />“What else? Anyway, they go in, we close the doors, we blow ‘em up. Easy. Watch.”
<br />Hordes of the infected charge into the bunker, grinning and howling. Not long before the entire bunker blows up.
<br />“Alright, I’ve gotta do the same at camp Zero. Remember the training.” the General got on his chopper and it took off.
<br />The pilot smirked at Su in a weird way before he got on the chopper.
<br />“WAIT! THE PILOT’S INFECTED! HE’S GONNA KILL THE GENERAL!” Su shouted at the top of his voice, picked up an Rpg and shot the chopper down.
<br />The General magically appeared beside him, and said “You stupid son of a”
<br />“Nap time’s over. Wake up buddy” Bar said.
<br />Su had been dreaming again. Dreaming of his training. Yet another dream horribly gone wrong ever since he aced the training.
<br />“Hey. Wake up. We’re almost there.” Chan was waking up Nith.<br /><br /></p>
<h1 id="the-mission">The mission</h1>
<p>Su, Bar, Chan and Nith were on a weapons salvage mission. The simplest one, albeit a tricky one, since they were embarking when
daylight was almost over. They were at their old dorm, to pick up a crate containing explosives. They didn’t have time during the
‘evacuation’, fighting off their friends who had just gotten infected. The whole dorm was a mess when they left, body parts flailing and blood squirting out of the bites their beloved friends left. They had no choice but to leave the weapons and all other supplies behind. Just send another crew on an errand mission to get it for them, right? Ironically, the command chose them to clean up their own mess.
<br />“Quick getaway, alright? No messing around. Just waltz in there, collect the crate, sprint your ass back here. We’ll be out of here in a minute.” Bar was the driver, and in charge of the mission.
<br />“Yea, mission detail was very clear. Pick up the crate, shake hands with our pals waiting for us, deliver their ‘present’ to you” Nith retorted. “I don’t like this place one bit.”
<br />“Neither do we. Just make it quick.” Chan was the peace keeper of the crew.
<br />Su and Nith reached the room that contained the explosives and began sifting through the mess to find usable ammunition. And there he was, Sam, sitting on his couch, right in front of Su, smoking one of the last cigars, grinning.<br />
<br />“Whoa, whoa, who do we have here? Hey Sam, how’s it going?” Su remarked in surprise.
<br />Sam, whose only last shred of consciousness was aiming at Su’s neck charged towards him in
excitement.
<br />“Whoa, hold your horses boy. Down. Down.” Su quietly said.</p>

<h1 id="the-infected">The Infected</h1>
<p>So this is the deal with the infected. They have a brain, and that’s pretty much it. It craves
for more of that sweet mix of heaven left in the world. When you’re being attacked by one, you can damage its body, but that does nothing; for their tenacity is plain stupid. They don’t care if they’re left limbless, or decapitated; the holy grail is holy enough to forgo any other physical pleasures.<br />
Now, in combat situations, DO NOT SHOOT THEM. JUST DON’T. They’ll shout so loud your ears will bleed and their pals rush knowing there’s fresh blood. You gotta understand that they don’t want you.
They’re not vampires. They’re more idiotic than that. They just kill you to prove a point. To turn you
into one of them, so you can join their army in this fight for ‘justice’.<br />
The best way to survive is to take those buggers down in a fist fight. The good ol’ way. Remember that they’re extremely weak until they’re provoked too much.</p>

<p><br />Su punched Sam right in the face, then jabbed him with a stick. Sam grabbed the stick, and Su kicked him at the calf, knocking him down.
“Pfffff” he yelled as he ran down the hallway.
Nith knocked down 3 of the infected, leaving them extremely confused as to how easily they lost the fight.
They got back in the car and sped off into the highway.</p>

<h1 id="better-is-worse">Better is worse</h1>
<p><br />It was already night when the group got close to the new dorm. There was a campfire beside one of the watch towers on the path. The man guarding it waved for them to stop.<br />
Bar rolled down the window “What’s the matter? Emergency?”
<br />“Umm..Yeah Kinda. Listen up, a convoy just passed me, almost everyone drunk.”
<br />“Drunk? What are you saying?” Chan questioned.
<br />“I know. So this is the news. Politician Rob’s son has passed away. This just broke out. You people look well educated, you know he was the main proponent of the experiment that went horribly wrong and caused this mess.”
<br />“So they were out celebrating. Umm what’s the concern?” Nith asked.
<br />“You guys know what happened the last time people were out ‘celebrating’.” the man replied.
<br />“Aight. We got the message. Thanks. And stay safe.” Bar knew what was going to happen.
<br />Su banged his head against the dashboard, and gasped. “I don’t wanna change dorms again.”
<br />Bar calmed him down, and pointed to the front. They had reached the dorm’s gate. <br />But it was barely recognizable, sprawling with cheerful people crowding the road, screaming and laughing. Some were going out, some were going in, but all of them had booze in their hands, and were clearly drunk.
<br />“Aight, I think we all need to worry now. A replay of last year.” Bar mumbled.
<br />“Jesus. Fuck! We need to evacuate. Get your things and let’s rendezvous in 10 minutes. Go go go!” Chan said.
<br />
Su reached his floor, and it was in complete chaos and disarray.<br />
“Hey, Rob’s son has died!”<br />
“That son of a bitch is deaaad!”<br />
“Oh yeahhh!”<br />
“Time for drinks!”<br />
“Hey Su, come on, where are you going? Join us, let’s get drunk and play cards, huh?”
<br />Su ignored everyone and rushed to his room. Mags was in there, and he seemed to be in a rush as well.
<br />“Yo, heard the news?” Su asked.
<br />“Yeah, Rob’s son is dead, right? Hahahaha. The infected got him. But hey, look man, I think I need to get some of the stuff, man.” Mags seemed anxious.
<br />“Cocaaaiinaa?”Su asked, knowing the answer.
<br />“Yeah, man. The F2 variant. I know you’ve stashed it somewhere here. Please man, I wanna relax.” Mags groaned.
<br />“But why the F2? Dude, that’s a protected resource. I can’t give that. Besides, I donno where I’ve stashed it.” Su was uncomfortable.
<br />Mash got up and started searching the room without Su’s consent.
<br />“Dude! Where is it? Aaaahh! Where is it, where is it, where is it?” Mags was getting cranky.
<br />Su knew something was wrong. He saw outside his room that Mags’ shoes were dirty. He had been outside. God knew what happened. Su was almost done packing his stuff.<br />
Outside the dorm, somwhere Downtown, some people saw the death as an opportunity to start a riot. They took to the streets, breaking the windows of stores, plundering and hooting and getting drunk.<br />
Maybe, just maybe they were making too much of a sound. Maybe, one of them had some ‘Cocaaiina’ in their backpack. Maybe that gave off a scent a tad too strong, a tad too long.<br />Maybe it looked like an invitation for the infected. Maybe these people weren’t prepared for an attack.</p>

<p>Back at the dorm, Su was now done packing, and he set out to the door, and asked Mags to tag along.
<br />Mags was now acting hysterical, and denied to come with him, and demanded that Su give him some of that goodness.
<br />Su noticed a scar on Mags’ neck when he turned around.
Su, now scared, said “Hey, you’re my brother. But if you don’t wanna come with me, it’s fine.<br /> I’m going, bye.”<br />
Mags now growled like a dog; his face had gotten slightly disfigured; he quietly bolted the door and advanced towards Su.</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="other" /><category term="Fiction" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What gets ‘em high? “We’re trying to shoot them down?” Su asked. “That does nothing” the General scoffed. He continued, “We need to blow ‘em up. That’s our only shot.” “And how do we do that” Su was thinking out loud. “Bait and switch. We fill up the bunkers with their “fix”.” “Coke? The F2 variant?” Su knew the plan. “What else? Anyway, they go in, we close the doors, we blow ‘em up. Easy. Watch.” Hordes of the infected charge into the bunker, grinning and howling. Not long before the entire bunker blows up. “Alright, I’ve gotta do the same at camp Zero. Remember the training.” the General got on his chopper and it took off. The pilot smirked at Su in a weird way before he got on the chopper. “WAIT! THE PILOT’S INFECTED! HE’S GONNA KILL THE GENERAL!” Su shouted at the top of his voice, picked up an Rpg and shot the chopper down. The General magically appeared beside him, and said “You stupid son of a” “Nap time’s over. Wake up buddy” Bar said. Su had been dreaming again. Dreaming of his training. Yet another dream horribly gone wrong ever since he aced the training. “Hey. Wake up. We’re almost there.” Chan was waking up Nith. The mission Su, Bar, Chan and Nith were on a weapons salvage mission. The simplest one, albeit a tricky one, since they were embarking when daylight was almost over. They were at their old dorm, to pick up a crate containing explosives. They didn’t have time during the ‘evacuation’, fighting off their friends who had just gotten infected. The whole dorm was a mess when they left, body parts flailing and blood squirting out of the bites their beloved friends left. They had no choice but to leave the weapons and all other supplies behind. Just send another crew on an errand mission to get it for them, right? Ironically, the command chose them to clean up their own mess. “Quick getaway, alright? No messing around. Just waltz in there, collect the crate, sprint your ass back here. We’ll be out of here in a minute.” Bar was the driver, and in charge of the mission. “Yea, mission detail was very clear. Pick up the crate, shake hands with our pals waiting for us, deliver their ‘present’ to you” Nith retorted. “I don’t like this place one bit.” “Neither do we. Just make it quick.” Chan was the peace keeper of the crew. Su and Nith reached the room that contained the explosives and began sifting through the mess to find usable ammunition. And there he was, Sam, sitting on his couch, right in front of Su, smoking one of the last cigars, grinning. “Whoa, whoa, who do we have here? Hey Sam, how’s it going?” Su remarked in surprise. Sam, whose only last shred of consciousness was aiming at Su’s neck charged towards him in excitement. “Whoa, hold your horses boy. Down. Down.” Su quietly said.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DUTY</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/11/duty.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DUTY" /><published>2018-01-11T06:34:49+00:00</published><updated>2018-01-11T06:34:49+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/11/duty</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/other/2018/01/11/duty.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="somewhere-in-a-snowy-part-of-the-world">Somewhere in a snowy part of the world</h1>
<p>K was listless. All his pals were fatigued. <br />The squad was still wading through
the snow on foot with their commander aboard the ATV, and the rest of the patrol followed suit.
Sun was just about to rise, so that was a relief. The chilly blizzard was eventually going to subside.<br />
“Ten more minutes to civilization!” one of the soldiers yelled.<br />
“Aight let’s stay frosty” replied K.<br />
“Pun?” asked his pal.<br />
“That’s all I got now.” K retorted with disdain.<br />
This was a simple infiltration mission, no hostiles expected on their way; the only enemy was the blizzard and the snow.<br />
The squad still had to remain stealthy, orders from the commander. Their vision was extremely limited, thanks to the weather.
<br />“I see houses” K shouted.
<br />“Dang it, we couldn’t see shit till we’re 20 feet away?” said J.
<br />“Good lord, where is everyone? There’s no people and all the doors are unlocked!” exclaimed P.
<br />“Bingo! Let’s use the houses to move, get in, get out through the back doors. We’ll have cover, and we’ll have heat.” K directed.
<br />“No, brother. We need to get there ASAP. No time to dally. Bear the cold for a few more minutes, would ya? We’re almost there” ordered his commander.
<br />“Makes sense” said K. “Aight people, straight ahead. Let’s keep going.”
As they made their way into the town for about 20 minutes, the blizzard got worse. Echo Squad was left blind as bats.
<br />U saw something. “Wait a minute, Halt! Take cover! Y and F are dead! They’ve been shot. Looks like a sniper! Watch out.”
The squad quickly took cover, and as they proceeded to move with caution, 3 others were shot in the head.
<br />“Holy cow! What’s happening?” P was scared.
<br /> 2 more of them got shot  right infront of them.
<br />“We’ve got to keep going as fast as possible. Run, so we don’t give them the time to aim. Run!” the Commander shouted at the top of his voice.
<br />K knew something was sketchy about this.
<br />“They’re using a drone to spot us. Heat signatures.” K whispered to P.
<br />“Doesn’t make sense. It’s our airspace.” P answered.
<br />“I know. Listen, follow me.” K insisted as he cut through to the side with P. They made their way around, running as quietly as possible. They eventually entered an abandoned robot manufacturing plant, and continued to run to the other side.
<br />“Holy molly, get down NOW! 12 O’ clock!” P said in a frantic tone.
<br />They spotted 2 enemy snipers camping on the first floor.
<br />“There’s definitely more of them. I hear radio chatter. They’re spread out all over the area.” P whispered.
<br />“There’s no way our patrol can make it through. We’ve gotta take them all out.” K infered.
<br />P continued, “Affirmative. These 2 first. On my mark. 3…2… “
Before they took the shot, the snipers got their heads blown out from the side. All P and K could hear were more suppressed rifles going off further to their right.
<br />“Not our squad. What the fuck is going on?” K exclaimed.
<br />One of the snipers got lucky, and retaliated. The gunshots were now loud and clear. K and P took cover and just listened with panic. There was a big shoot out for a while, and then the sounds stopped.
<br />As K and P got up the ladder to take a look, detonators set off simulatenously, making a huge noise, and mangling the bodies.
<br />“Our guests wanted to make sure everyone’s dead. I believe they’ve left.”
<br />K and P took snipers from a corpse and looked for them. They could see an ATV speed away at a distance.<br />
It then stopped briefly, and their commander got into it, and then it vanished into the snow.
<br />After a few minutes of deliberation, K realized what was happening.
<br />“They’re making it seem like a war has been started.”
<br />“What do you mean? We’re already in war” P was confused.
<br />“It has just aggravated. Now this will be a whole different war. <b>We’ve started a bigger one.</b>
<br />And someone’s gonna use this to keep all the eyes away from something else, something much bigger than this.”</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="other" /><category term="SpyGame" /><category term="Fiction" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere in a snowy part of the world K was listless. All his pals were fatigued. The squad was still wading through the snow on foot with their commander aboard the ATV, and the rest of the patrol followed suit. Sun was just about to rise, so that was a relief. The chilly blizzard was eventually going to subside. “Ten more minutes to civilization!” one of the soldiers yelled. “Aight let’s stay frosty” replied K. “Pun?” asked his pal. “That’s all I got now.” K retorted with disdain. This was a simple infiltration mission, no hostiles expected on their way; the only enemy was the blizzard and the snow. The squad still had to remain stealthy, orders from the commander. Their vision was extremely limited, thanks to the weather. “I see houses” K shouted. “Dang it, we couldn’t see shit till we’re 20 feet away?” said J. “Good lord, where is everyone? There’s no people and all the doors are unlocked!” exclaimed P. “Bingo! Let’s use the houses to move, get in, get out through the back doors. We’ll have cover, and we’ll have heat.” K directed. “No, brother. We need to get there ASAP. No time to dally. Bear the cold for a few more minutes, would ya? We’re almost there” ordered his commander. “Makes sense” said K. “Aight people, straight ahead. Let’s keep going.” As they made their way into the town for about 20 minutes, the blizzard got worse. Echo Squad was left blind as bats. U saw something. “Wait a minute, Halt! Take cover! Y and F are dead! They’ve been shot. Looks like a sniper! Watch out.” The squad quickly took cover, and as they proceeded to move with caution, 3 others were shot in the head. “Holy cow! What’s happening?” P was scared. 2 more of them got shot right infront of them. “We’ve got to keep going as fast as possible. Run, so we don’t give them the time to aim. Run!” the Commander shouted at the top of his voice. K knew something was sketchy about this. “They’re using a drone to spot us. Heat signatures.” K whispered to P. “Doesn’t make sense. It’s our airspace.” P answered. “I know. Listen, follow me.” K insisted as he cut through to the side with P. They made their way around, running as quietly as possible. They eventually entered an abandoned robot manufacturing plant, and continued to run to the other side. “Holy molly, get down NOW! 12 O’ clock!” P said in a frantic tone. They spotted 2 enemy snipers camping on the first floor. “There’s definitely more of them. I hear radio chatter. They’re spread out all over the area.” P whispered. “There’s no way our patrol can make it through. We’ve gotta take them all out.” K infered. P continued, “Affirmative. These 2 first. On my mark. 3…2… “ Before they took the shot, the snipers got their heads blown out from the side. All P and K could hear were more suppressed rifles going off further to their right. “Not our squad. What the fuck is going on?” K exclaimed. One of the snipers got lucky, and retaliated. The gunshots were now loud and clear. K and P took cover and just listened with panic. There was a big shoot out for a while, and then the sounds stopped. As K and P got up the ladder to take a look, detonators set off simulatenously, making a huge noise, and mangling the bodies. “Our guests wanted to make sure everyone’s dead. I believe they’ve left.” K and P took snipers from a corpse and looked for them. They could see an ATV speed away at a distance. It then stopped briefly, and their commander got into it, and then it vanished into the snow. After a few minutes of deliberation, K realized what was happening. “They’re making it seem like a war has been started.” “What do you mean? We’re already in war” P was confused. “It has just aggravated. Now this will be a whole different war. We’ve started a bigger one. And someone’s gonna use this to keep all the eyes away from something else, something much bigger than this.”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lightning</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/other/2016/07/23/lightning.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lightning" /><published>2016-07-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-07-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/other/2016/07/23/lightning</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/other/2016/07/23/lightning.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="game">Game</h1>
<p>As incessant rains lashed out on the village, the game reached the final round.
Tensions soared, concentration peaked and minds were doing a zillion calculations every second.
All the roads were over a feet deep in water, and one could find the reflections of the midnight moon in the waters.
Neither the loud rains nor the abrupt thunders could tamper with their game. They were in the zone. Playing the game. Phase locked.
And after what seemed to be a very short time,the game ended. Jay finally won.<br />
<br />‘Woo Hoo !’
<br />‘Not again.’ said Su.
<br />‘Don’t do your neigh. Please.’ said Prady.
<br />‘Yee Haa !’
<br />‘There we go.’ said Goutham.
<br />‘So you get your money back.’ said Su.
<br />‘Yes, I do! ‘ exclaimed Jay.
<br />‘Alright, let’s take a break.’
<br />‘Yeah, let’s take some pictures of the view.’
<br />‘Great. But don’t make a bokeh again. It sucks.’
<br />‘I like ‘em. So buzz off.’
<br />‘Bzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz’.
<br />‘Peace. Won’t argue with you.’
<br />They made their way out of the room on the top floor of the mansion to the patio, Su started clicking pictures,
and Jay and Prad started smoking.
<br />Hills encompassed the village on all sides, and lightning struck them repeatedly. The sky was eerily dark, and the moon was now nowhere to be seen.
<br />‘This is odd’ remarked Goutham.
<br />The lightning wasn’t ordinary. There was too much of it, and the guys knew something wasn’t right.
Through the rain, on the other side of the village, they spotted something.
There was one little area on a hill where lightning struck almost periodically,
and after four or five cycles, about ten adjacent places up there would get hit by a wide line of almost blinding light.
Though they initially dismissed the idea, curiosity got the better of them, and they soon started making plans to get there.
<br />‘Okay, how?’
<br />‘The panther’ Prady said.
<br />‘Really, bruh?’
<br />‘We’ll get drenched to death.’
<br />‘Oh come on. The panther will always be our official adventure vehicle we all agreed.’
<br />The panther was an old topless 4x4 Jeep they had bought together. Rain couldn’t stop their insane quest for adventure.
<br />‘Panther it is, then. Let’s roll!’
<br />‘WE’RE GONNA DIE!’ Jay hollered.
<br />‘HAHAHAHA’
<br />They got in the panther, with their usual outfits: overcoats, hats, torchlights, backpacks and unrivalled bravado.
The panther easily made its way through the water into the jungle. They had already gotten drenched, but that wasn’t the priority on their minds.
It was the mysterious appearance of this supposed lightning.
<br />As the panther waded through the huge rocks and the dense trees and the puddles of water, they realised that they were so alone in the darkness.
Only the sounds of the vicious rain hitting the rocks could be heard, apart from the scary thuds from the thunders, and the continuous splashes of water off the panther’s tires.
Slowly ascending the hill, they looked back at the village which lied at the chief depression of the hills. Apart from that, there wasn’t any light, and darkness dominated the world.
<br />The strikes on the peak ahead got stronger and louder.
The panther couldn’t take them any farther as the forest grew denser. But the relentless crew got down and made their way to the destination, staying close to each other.
The wind grew stronger, and the rain drifted along its direction.
<br />‘This would make a perfect setup for a movie.’ Su was excited.
<br />‘Would it be tragic at the end too?’ Prad joked.
<br />‘Stop it guys, you’re scaring me!’ said Goutham.</p>
<h1 id="peak">Peak</h1>
<p>Just as they reached the peak, the biggest group of strikes hit close to them, and the shock carried by the impact grounded them.
As they gathered themselves up, what they saw baffled them. The lights in the village were gone. Hell, they couldn’t even make out if the village was still there.
<br />The sky was now more like outerspace, completely dark,only seen when lightning appeared.
<br />The rain had stopped, only god knew when. The ground beneath was already drying up, too freaking fast for them to believe.
As they still recovered from the shock, the most unexpected thing happened.
<br />Out of the blue, something lit up in the sky, and whooshed past the hills, making a shrill, unbearable sound.
<br />The light wasn’t white. It was blue.
They thought it was a comet, but this thing flew so freaking close to the hills. And what was that sound? Like an old lady’s whine.
<br />What in the world just happened?
<br />Whatever it was, and whatever just happened, they knew life wouldn’t be the same again. Their hearts began to race, and as shock receded, adrenaline took over.
<br />They looked at each other in unison.</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="other" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game As incessant rains lashed out on the village, the game reached the final round. Tensions soared, concentration peaked and minds were doing a zillion calculations every second. All the roads were over a feet deep in water, and one could find the reflections of the midnight moon in the waters. Neither the loud rains nor the abrupt thunders could tamper with their game. They were in the zone. Playing the game. Phase locked. And after what seemed to be a very short time,the game ended. Jay finally won. ‘Woo Hoo !’ ‘Not again.’ said Su. ‘Don’t do your neigh. Please.’ said Prady. ‘Yee Haa !’ ‘There we go.’ said Goutham. ‘So you get your money back.’ said Su. ‘Yes, I do! ‘ exclaimed Jay. ‘Alright, let’s take a break.’ ‘Yeah, let’s take some pictures of the view.’ ‘Great. But don’t make a bokeh again. It sucks.’ ‘I like ‘em. So buzz off.’ ‘Bzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz’. ‘Peace. Won’t argue with you.’ They made their way out of the room on the top floor of the mansion to the patio, Su started clicking pictures, and Jay and Prad started smoking. Hills encompassed the village on all sides, and lightning struck them repeatedly. The sky was eerily dark, and the moon was now nowhere to be seen. ‘This is odd’ remarked Goutham. The lightning wasn’t ordinary. There was too much of it, and the guys knew something wasn’t right. Through the rain, on the other side of the village, they spotted something. There was one little area on a hill where lightning struck almost periodically, and after four or five cycles, about ten adjacent places up there would get hit by a wide line of almost blinding light. Though they initially dismissed the idea, curiosity got the better of them, and they soon started making plans to get there. ‘Okay, how?’ ‘The panther’ Prady said. ‘Really, bruh?’ ‘We’ll get drenched to death.’ ‘Oh come on. The panther will always be our official adventure vehicle we all agreed.’ The panther was an old topless 4x4 Jeep they had bought together. Rain couldn’t stop their insane quest for adventure. ‘Panther it is, then. Let’s roll!’ ‘WE’RE GONNA DIE!’ Jay hollered. ‘HAHAHAHA’ They got in the panther, with their usual outfits: overcoats, hats, torchlights, backpacks and unrivalled bravado. The panther easily made its way through the water into the jungle. They had already gotten drenched, but that wasn’t the priority on their minds. It was the mysterious appearance of this supposed lightning. As the panther waded through the huge rocks and the dense trees and the puddles of water, they realised that they were so alone in the darkness. Only the sounds of the vicious rain hitting the rocks could be heard, apart from the scary thuds from the thunders, and the continuous splashes of water off the panther’s tires. Slowly ascending the hill, they looked back at the village which lied at the chief depression of the hills. Apart from that, there wasn’t any light, and darkness dominated the world. The strikes on the peak ahead got stronger and louder. The panther couldn’t take them any farther as the forest grew denser. But the relentless crew got down and made their way to the destination, staying close to each other. The wind grew stronger, and the rain drifted along its direction. ‘This would make a perfect setup for a movie.’ Su was excited. ‘Would it be tragic at the end too?’ Prad joked. ‘Stop it guys, you’re scaring me!’ said Goutham. Peak Just as they reached the peak, the biggest group of strikes hit close to them, and the shock carried by the impact grounded them. As they gathered themselves up, what they saw baffled them. The lights in the village were gone. Hell, they couldn’t even make out if the village was still there. The sky was now more like outerspace, completely dark,only seen when lightning appeared. The rain had stopped, only god knew when. The ground beneath was already drying up, too freaking fast for them to believe. As they still recovered from the shock, the most unexpected thing happened. Out of the blue, something lit up in the sky, and whooshed past the hills, making a shrill, unbearable sound. The light wasn’t white. It was blue. They thought it was a comet, but this thing flew so freaking close to the hills. And what was that sound? Like an old lady’s whine. What in the world just happened? Whatever it was, and whatever just happened, they knew life wouldn’t be the same again. Their hearts began to race, and as shock receded, adrenaline took over. They looked at each other in unison.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Great Destroyer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/other/2015/09/23/the-great-destroyer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Great Destroyer" /><published>2015-09-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2015-09-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/other/2015/09/23/the-great-destroyer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/other/2015/09/23/the-great-destroyer.html"><![CDATA[<p>He was staring into absolute darkness.Nothing else, just plain void. There was no sound, no smell, no sight, no sense of  touch either. He felt weightless, spaceless. But behind him was something he didn’t want to see. He knew he had finally reached his ‘destiny’. And he was scared to see what the creator looked like.</p>

<p>He finally mustered the courage to turn. He turned.He turned, and experienced the ineffable. Before him was a figure, glowing in the dark.He realised this was outer space, and the figure stood on a one dimensional platform. Stood? No. It was moving violently, shaking all its parts. Now he could make out the shape. It resembled a human form. But gosh, it was atleast a million times bigger than him, and he could see the eyes too. The eyes were flaming red, lava pouring out from them. Its glow blinded him.Its hair flew all over the universe. And the whole universe started shaking with its moves, resonating with his steps. Was he dancing ? What was happening?</p>

<p>Accompanying the dance was noise he couldn’t bear. The sounds were absolutely disjoint glitches of varying kinds, too loud and shrill that he started bleeding and screaming. But he caught the rhythm soon and suddenly, they all appeared to be in perfect sync. The sound was surreal, the perfect embodiment of art. It was music.It was music at its purest form. He couldn’t believe what was happening. Since he knew he was in his mind, was it a virus? That was what pathogens looked like?
No. Was it a sub-atomic particle? Was it God ? Was it god? Was it god? It was god? That was god !</p>

<p>Suddenly he was transported with all kinds of emotions.He was scared and overwhelmed,he was laughing and crying,he was calm and angry and ecstatic; and joined the figure which continued to dance with fury, joy and vigor while the god music continued to blare. The music reached its crescendo now.He felt weightless, he felt invincible dancing and jumping like that.Tears stormed down from his eyes. He knew what he wanted to do. He wanted to ‘surrender’ himself to god. He wanted to die.Merge with god.Become a part of him. Is this what the vedas talked about? He was a rational person, but he couldn’t believe what was happening.</p>

<p>All his senses now worked in unison and gave him the unified sense. The one only attainable by god. He grew in space, and time. He was turning into god. He could see the space, the earth, its people, the zillion other planets thriving with life, which appeared so close to earth. He could see the beginning, he could see the end. He could see the beings, calling out to him. He could see the infinite and the infinitesimal. All through his mind.
<br />He turned into the Great Destroyer.</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="other" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[He was staring into absolute darkness.Nothing else, just plain void. There was no sound, no smell, no sight, no sense of touch either. He felt weightless, spaceless. But behind him was something he didn’t want to see. He knew he had finally reached his ‘destiny’. And he was scared to see what the creator looked like.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Square Zero</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/other/1995/01/01/squarezero.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Square Zero" /><published>1995-01-01T10:22:23+00:00</published><updated>1995-01-01T10:22:23+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/other/1995/01/01/squarezero</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/other/1995/01/01/squarezero.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="looks-like-im-doing-this">Looks like I’m doing this.</h1>
<p>Our mind is a constant source of new ideas and thoughts, which often end up garbled after we move on with time, and new
ideas and thoughts supersede these pieces of brilliance we once had.
Bookkeeping is essential to record one’s state of mind, and for retrospection. I remember the times when my mind was
bustling with fantastic theories, that I couldn’t keep track of them after a while. Most of them have become obscure with time;
I have forgotten all the specifics and the minute details. That is when I started blogging, to try and keep track of them
as well as to share these with people who might be fascinated by the same things as I am, which has also introduced me to
some amazing people.</p>

<h1 id="voice">Voice</h1>
<p>Talking of the interest in sharing things, I have developed a new interest in developing a strong voice over a lot of topics,
and sharing them. Voice is absolutely necessary for any person over anything. That’s how people develop perspective, and that’s
how they build character. However, just developing a voice could be detrimental, if it’s not shared and debated and questioned.
Sharing this voice out in the open with confidantes, or friends, or the public leads to debate and discussions and arguments, often fruitful.</p>

<h1 id="under-the-rug">Under the rug</h1>
<p>Moreover, I badly need to take time off consuming content and put it to good use analyzing and creating. The past few months have
been a true eye opener for me, and I was exposed to an array of critical topics like politics, human psychology, the big picture,
superstitions, and decisive observations on a lot of things that happen behind the scenes. This will be a place where I can analyze
what I’ve consumed, and develop a perspective. The interest has also extended to influence others.</p>

<h1 id="this-is-good-right">This is good, right?</h1>
<p>If everything else is a delusion, this is atleast a good way to spend time. This will also aid me in refining my vocab and communication style. I’ve always wanted to learn and master critical writing, and writing in general. And lastly, this will also make me tinker more with github and Jekyll and NodeJs and a plethora of the other options out there on the web.</p>

<h1 id="box-of-chocolates">Box of chocolates</h1>
<p>This is going to be awesome! I’m gonna write fiction, non-fiction, some songs maybe, and what not. Just that I’ll take more time
developing and refining the articles, to make it a notch better than <a href="http://tlojarus.blogspot.in/">TLOj</a>.<br />
Here’s to a bright future filled with hope and better conscience!</p>]]></content><author><name>Jevgenij Ivanov</name></author><category term="other" /><category term="Discourse" /><category term="NonFiction" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like I’m doing this. Our mind is a constant source of new ideas and thoughts, which often end up garbled after we move on with time, and new ideas and thoughts supersede these pieces of brilliance we once had. Bookkeeping is essential to record one’s state of mind, and for retrospection. I remember the times when my mind was bustling with fantastic theories, that I couldn’t keep track of them after a while. Most of them have become obscure with time; I have forgotten all the specifics and the minute details. That is when I started blogging, to try and keep track of them as well as to share these with people who might be fascinated by the same things as I am, which has also introduced me to some amazing people.]]></summary></entry></feed>